So hello friends welcome to my channel the
above brother our Activa 4G met with an
accident on 13th April 2021
so brother let me tell you how this accident happened
brother the
van of the vehicle was coming from the flyover at a high speed
so it cut our subscriber's car completely
and
on our left side we had put it on insurance
and our insurance claim was done by doing this so if
you like this video then
I will
show you the photos of how it happened
now brother it looked like spider-man a lot brother it was
completely broken brother this one is also of complete
statement then I will show you the photos
how much fun it is to have an Activa
in an accident so come on as if
you have understood this photo and this accident happened
in April we got it on April
and we were subscribed
so I will tell you how much
denting and painting was done on it and
how much it cost me so subscribe what
documents will you have to submit when I
What documents do
you need, I will maintain it green on the side
and I will tell you like this,
first of all you need a copy of whatever I say in the Aadhar card,
brother, first of all you need a copy of Aadhar card, PAN
card and RC and if you mean
old insurance, then its valid office is there
and if you have got new
insurance then you will get the copy of that as well and the
password is also there in your account, its
passbook is there and to
claim insurance, everything is mentioned in the FIR
so that you can find out where the accident happened,
when it happened, how it happened and at what time, on
which day it happened, then everything is maintained in the FIR and an
FIR is also filed but if you have
not done this then brother
some showroom owners give it to Allah and do it,
some showroom owners do
not do it, they will say can't we do this,
Vinay figure, but we have
not taken any action yet, it was our shop, some of
your such yogas, then
this is some mehndi percentage, some main
documents for you to claim insurance
and let me tell you that after all the damage was done
that it is fit for business today,
denting-painting has been found on it, I will show that
And the documents that will appear on your screen will appear
and I will
put the description in mine, so brother, I will show you as
in the photo what all happened in the filling,
brother, this happened and this side also happened,
brother, this entire site was gone, this one was gone,
brother, and this bag was gone, brother, and now
this has happened because all this is new,
and this, you are not subscribed here,
remember, it happened inside, you
saw it in such a photo, this is a new partner, brother,
see, I have not put any new part in it, brother, I have
not put many things in it, and brother, look at this,
how much kind of gas is there in the rear here and on
that side, I will show you, look at these, there is
no difference at all in it, so this is the difference that came
after the accident, and look at this, it is getting separated from here
also, it must be visible, I do Nagku
Vikas, so look at this, brother, and
here brother, this has also been done, so guys,
I am seeing, you
can carefully look at your scooter, see
here also, is it rising, is that side good
or not, so you can see here
also  It is a little bit like this
and brother here, the way it is,
we have not done it completely, we have
not done it at all, look here it is the same
and this has happened, it is left on the side, brother, it was a
disease on the left side, brother, it happened
on the side, it did not happen on this side, nothing happens,
it is going as before, so the thing which
I liked the most about Dubai Insurance is
this scrub in an accidental manner, they do not have this also here
because they hate it and I told the
service center people here and
look here, Meghnad stand here also does
not say anything to them, they are not in service at
all, they subscribed to this channel
and this one which was also torn,
I subscribed and they say,
hey brother, how can this not be done,
look, it is completely torn, you did
not even put this from here, the one above the net,
friend, it has increased, now brother, what should be done,
brother, like we have done denting and painting here also,
they will
not see any scratch here, they are not even doing it, they are
charging a little money, they are not doing it,
this is useless but this thing is not at all  I
mean I didn't do anything at all, you can share this MS Word
and it's not at all here
now it looks something like this here too and
this bumper is not at all to be subscribed so by
the love I did it on the damage that happened
and there was nothing improved around them
I will show you more brother, you have messed up my
mind and I mean and here I have
put two more brother what are you doing, it is in Patan it
looks like the same in
Haryana, it is also known that it has been painted
all now the bike has been completely ruined brother
school e love nothing has been fixed I mean on which the
day is fine now on this side look at the insurance side,
see the subscription is complete,
everything is not there
[Music]
yes this will tell you about the bill
how much it cost me, you must have seen the card support inside that thing,
it was completely cracked and when I was
doing one more thing there, I mean I was starting it and
checking it with the rear brake,
so they opened it again
and I saw brother good night which we
saw in our first video which I
Meena had got it modified for four mediators, so I had
this thought, but brother, the date has changed, so there is nothing in it, so I will have to get a
button
put in it, okay, I can remove it, it smells like
wires inside, so we will go some other time, I will get a button put in it,
now the
torch light mobile, come on, you must not have seen it,
it was damaged, we could have
talked about subscription till the bottom, then it is
exactly the same thing
that this brother is denting-painting, brother, how much is it, if it is
650, that too has
not been done properly, dating in or 26650, I had taken it for
Delhi Great Robbery and it is
select printing, this should be charged ₹500, the
party doing it,
I did ₹500 for printing and
in this, I also took ₹300 for opening and closing,
so where will the total fourth tab be kept, it will be
9th, I do this 436, I do not know
what all, I made it 5427, laughingly
said that 5427 here
49 for ₹10 for over 400 files and I
should have told you that it was starting so subscribe and the
accused of subscription, so let me tell you
that you had asked the subscription manager,
he was telling that it depends on the top that the
cent is deducted on the subscription, he was telling that I will
see it, so this was today's video, if you liked
my video then like and
subscribe to our channel, till then
bye-bye